strangebeaver.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy – Strange Beaver

StrangeBeaver.com and it’s affiliates will, under no circumstances, share your personal information with any other entity. Personal information including, but not limited to, e-mail address, postal mailing address and phone numbers, are only for the purpose of communicating with StrangeBeaver.com staff and you. Some companies try to sell mailing lists to make extra cash and since that’s a total dick thing to do we won’t share your information. 

That being said, we have to include the fine print for our advertisers:

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.>
